Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ojoolayode-0744b775 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

RabbitMQ
.NET Framework
Spring MVC

Languages

English Yoruba

Ojo Olayode

Software and Devops Engineer at Maxut Consulting Nigeria

Summary

Experienced Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in SQL, NoSQL, Java, C#, Node Js, ASP.NET MVC, PHP, Javascript, jQuery, Angular Javascript, Android development with kotlin. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) focused on SLT from the University of Ado-Ekiti.

Experience

Maxut Consulting Software Engineer June 2018 - Present (5 years 8 months) USA, Nigeria

Implementation of 2FA and securing Digital Banking channel for Commercial Bank Using VASCO(One Span) SDK

Humbertechnologie Web Developer January 2014 - January 2017 (3 years 1 month) Lagos

INS

Web developer December 2013 - September 2014 (10 months) Lagos

Education

NIIT Institute

Certificate in Java SE and EE, Computer Software Engineering (2012 - 2012)

University of Ado-Ekiti Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.), Microbiology